If you like the video, please like and subscribe to the channel!
Winner's Reward Time!
20,000 yen worth of exquisite Chinese food!
We're here to eat!
Yay!
I'm sorry, but...
When did this happen?
The outfit.
I think it's cute.
It's cute, but what's going on all of a sudden?
The inner lining's still different.
The innerwear, too.
They're not the usual ones.
I don't know if it's something I can show you.
It'll take a while.
Oh, uh...
They're used, aren't they?
Used? What's that?
Quickly?
Yay!
Ta-da!
It's so thin.
In the middle of the project
We, Yoshida and Shiozaki's team won.
Oh, yes...
Why is Matsumura here today?
I'm here because I did well on my exams.
I speak a little Chinese.
Oh, really?
Yes, you do.
Who are you?
Yangqi. Chunhai.
Haoqi.
No, no, no.
Yanqi Typhoon is Shiozaki Dazhong.
Yanchi means Shiozaki or something.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
May I ask for a letter?
Shiozaki can read the award.
Yes, thank you very much
And thank you for taking that exam
Thank you very much
We've prepared an exquisite Chinese meal for the three of you today
However, it's not fun to just let them eat for free
It's no fun to just let them eat for free.
I'm going to challenge you to a game.
No way!
It's not funny.
If you lose, you get the food.
What?
There's a prize for the winner.
Good luck.
That's not exactly what I heard.
I'm here because I won.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I said I'd feed you as a reward.
I said, "No, no, no.
Then we'll have a showdown.
Wait a minute.
I won!
You're so determined!
I've never seen anyone push me with a hammer.
No, but... I heard this is the star.
I don't think so.
I heard this is the star.
So let's go.
Yes, sir.
So here we are.
Eat with proper manners.
Chinese food
Kao Qi
Is it difficult to understand the manners of Chinese food?
I don't know...
It's pretty difficult now, isn't it?
Oh, no, it's difficult!
You will hear a sound when there is an NG.
Please stop your chopsticks immediately.
Wow~ that's tough!
Or eat up before you are recruited.
I'll do my best! Thank you very much!
Bon appétit!
Wait a minute.
This is where it all started.
For example, if Daichi makes a mistake, we'll eat it too.
That's for sure.
You don't have to drink any more tea.
No, no, no.
You're right.
We don't have to drink tea.
I'm going for it. I'll have a cup of tea.
I wonder if he'll start with someone younger than him.
I think we'd get along.
Yeah, something like that.
No, no, but someone who's old enough...
They take what they want to eat to themselves.
Maybe it's the old people.
It's true, he's like, "I'll take it first.
Hey! Come on in, bro!
Come on in, bro.Come in, brother, so char quickly.
Turn it with your right hand.
You turn it with your right hand.
I don't know if it's okay this way or not.
Ah!
Yes, sir.
Clockwise.
Hey!
Gacha wanted, dry mouth, right?
Dry mouth?
No, I'm not supposed to go to Shibuya.
No, no, no, too Shibuya!
You want a salad? Salad?
Shrimp.
Here, here, here...
What is it?
Be careful how you take it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It doesn't matter how you take it.
No, but I have a spoon.
If the spoon gets moved, I don't know what's going on.
No, no, no, no, no! No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
You want to do it on that plate?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
And then it'll come out to you, right?
No!
Is there such a thing?
If you take the asparagus, you can't open it, right?
Next Daichi, you can do the same thing.
Oh, okay, okay.
Oh, it works!
Yay, yay, yay!
I'll buy it!
Oh, yeah!
It's okay.
It's good.
What?
The way you hold your chopsticks.
Yes, well, I'm only allowed to use the bus.
What do you mean? Oh, what?
Oh, you mean this is not allowed?
That's right.
Okay. Okay.
Recruitment? Recruiting.
You're cheating!
Didn't you win already?
Huh?
You...
Hey, hey, hey!
You... you... you sacked...
Wait a minute, that's too tough, too tough, too tough.
Of course I had to see Jin-chan.
But before that, who'd have thought of this?
You and Jin quit for a minute?
I'm quitting.
I'm not stuck with Jin.
Can I tell you something?
Can I say something?
Let's give it a shot, okay?
Soup's too hard, huh?
Oh, my God.
I thought it was supposed to go with this. This one.
Of course it does.
Isn't there some kind of way to put this? This one.
Ha-ha-ha! There is!
I'm scared.
Why are you doing this while eating?
Cooley!
Oh, this is not good.
I can't make any more mistakes.
I can't make a mistake.
You're right.
Come on in.
Wow.
Oh, wow.
It's so good.
Oh, this is delicious.
Oh, it's so good!
Yum!
Oh, this is so good!
Oh, my God.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
лиш displayed
I'm going out at night s 1 heel stafer
litter game organizations yeah ne me
back and forth
I didn't hit it.
It's okay, I'm still apologizing, but it's growing.
It's not increasing.
I'll see you later.
Let's go to the yearbook.
Yearling.
All the year-olds do is eat.
You've got to realize...
Seriously, don't screw this up.
You've got to put it in there,
No, no, no, it's okay.
Daichi, fill it up right away.
Eat up, eat up, eat up!
I've got this.I've got this.
There's a lot of rice on the table.
I think that garbage is in there.
I have to change that plate.
Are you an idiot?
Hey! You're an idiot!
Wait a minute. Okay.
Hey, I'll change the plate.
I'll change the plate. Of course I'll change the plate.
What are you doing? You already started.
Bean-curd soup with hot spicy sauce.
Ui!
You!
You have to mix it.
We don't mix it in Japan!
Bean-curd soup with red pepper!
Before you know it, there's nothing left but spare ribs.
I don't know how to eat those!
Wait a minute, what do we do with that?
This isn't working. Give me this plate.
Yes, yes, yes.
Why are you taking it? With your hands?
This one?
If you take this with your hands, you can run.
Wipe your hands.
You're so beautiful. Show off.
You're making a bad face, sir.
I'll take it with my hand.
Don't do that!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Put it back, put it back, put it back!
Why?
Because of you.
Because it's you.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I hate Chinese food.
Isn't it recorded?
Kaito Miyachika's idea
Rice eyes
I have a suggestion.
There are three of us.
Until the third inning is out.
I won't be recruited.
Please.
Sweet. Sweet?
You were nice then. You were nice the first time.
Mix it up. Mix it up.
Just a dash. - Just a dash?
Just a little bit. So, did you mix this? Just a little bit of unmixed.
Just a millimeter or so of the bun.
Which way? Did you mix it?
Did you mix it? If I say I did, I did.
If I say I didn't, I didn't.
Oh, I see. I see.
Oh, wow.
Oh, that looks good.
Then it might be bad.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Soup first.
Oh, but I'm surprised.
The boo-boo overdifferentiation isn't working at all.
It's not moving, is it?
People don't seem to care that much.
Just keep doing what you're doing, like you've always done.
That's right.
If something's not quite right, they'll just smile like that, like it's delicious.
Like, "Oh, that looks so good!
You should see it.
Oh, that's good. - You can put a lot of food in there.
It's good, isn't it?
It's already reacting to the powder, so there's no limit to how much you can put in.
You can take some here, take some there.
I don't do that very often.
When do you think we're gonna do that?
No, no, no, no, no.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. It's okay. It's still okay.
Let's eat soon.
No rinsing.
No rinsing for now.
Okay, okay, okay.
And you're left-handed, right?
You're okay.
I'm left-handed.
Forgive my hand.
Bon appétit!
Oh, my God!
It looks good on you.
Wait a minute.
I just put my left hand on my right hand.
Put it like this.
Like this.
Ha-ha-ha.
It's okay. It's okay. You can still eat.
Put it on.
Just stop.Let's just stop.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
He doesn't need chopsticks.
You don't want chopsticks?
No?
I don't need chopsticks.
I'll just put them on.
So did you use them? If you say, "Did you use it?
No, I didn't use it.
I say, "You didn't use it.
I did.
How much do you want me to spend?
You know?
Ha-ha-ha.
Shake it out, man. Just take a big dump.
Oh.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
That's the right one.
This is it. This is it.
That's what I'm talking about.
I don't need it.
If you don't want this, it's good.
That's why it's so good.
That's good.
I finally said it.
I already know.
I'll have one too.
I'll eat with you when we're all lined up.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh!
I'll have a lot of drinks.
Yeah.
Just keep repeating this, right?
Yeah. - Yeah.
It's so good.
Yum!
It's so good!
I've done this with chopsticks twice now.
I shouldn't use chopsticks!
Put them in the lentil bowl like this.
I'm sorry, guys.
I'm sorry.
Eat while you still can, guys.
It's my fault. I'm sorry.
Eat it the Japanese way now.
I've been slurping it the Japanese way for years.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What's the matter, it stain?
No, no, no, no.
But I'm sitting next to someone.
That's impossible.
Oh-ho-ho
You, over here.
You're both sure to pass through at one time
ahahahahahaha
We did well on the entrance exam.
Do you want some sweets?
Of course I want some sweets.
Of course I want to eat sweets.
I was very strict.
But the owner said I could have some sweets.
I can have some sweets.
Thank you.
I knew you were kind.
You're very kind. Thank you.
That's so light.
Yum!
Delicious.
Oh, wow.
This is amazing.
What is this?
It's like coffee jelly, but...
It's a little bit mellow.
It's all new.
Did you like it?
It was good.
I handled it, so I guess it was okay.
The hardest part of cooking on an empty stomach is...
The hardest part of cooking on an empty stomach is when there's a dish that looks so good
But you can't eat it.
I felt the same way as Yuu.
Today's title "Yuu's feeling
Punishment game group
Oh, um...
Uh...
It's a deserted island, right?
I got a call suddenly.
Yeah. - What?
What? Like...
Something.
Something with beef.
I want to say something heartbreaking.
Beef?
He asked me to say a heart-warming story using beef as the key word.
Yeah. - What?
What?
What?Huh?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
The end.